http://www.tierrafarm.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Our online privacy notice describes what personal data and non-personal data we may collect from you, how we collect that data, how we protect it, and how we may share it. We also describe what you can do to access and change the data we’ve collected, and how you can limit our sharing of it. Our online privacy notice also provides details on how to opt-out from having your personal data collected. Our online privacy notice applies only to information collected through our website and not to information that may be collected offline.
This document governs the privacy notice of our website, www.TierraFarmStore.com. This website is owned and operated by Tierra Farm, 2424 State Route 203, Valatie, NY 12184.
Effective date: June 6, 2018Last modified: June 6, 2018
Term Definitions
“Non-personal data” is information that in no way can personally identify any individual.
“Personal data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by name, identification number, location, online identifier or to any factor specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, economic, cultural or social identity of that person. Personal data is, in many ways, the same as Personally Identifiable Information (PII). However, personal data is broader in scope and covers more data.
“Personal Information” is both device information and order information.
Your Consent
By continuing to use our website, you consent to our online privacy notice.
Information We Collect
Generally, you control the amount and type of information that you provide to us when using our website.
When you visit our site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on our site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse our site.
Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through our site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers and PayPal account details), email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
How We Use Your Personal Information
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through our site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you;
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with our site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
Sharing Your Personal Information
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store; you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.
We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use our site; you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting the following links:
Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
Google - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
Do Not Track
Please note that we do not alter our site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
Data Retention
When you place an order through our site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
Security Policy
Our website is secured using the industry standard, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption. It encrypts all your personal information, including name and email, so that it cannot be read over the internet. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee against the loss or misuse of your personal data or secure data transmission over the internet because of its nature.
Changes to Our Privacy Notice
We reserve the right to change our privacy notice at any time. If our company decides to change this privacy notice, we will post those changes on this page so that our users and customers are always up to date on what information we collect, use, and disclose. When we change the policy, we will update the “last modified” date at the top of this page. Your continued use of our website, services, and products after any change to this privacy notice will constitute your acceptance of that change.
Questions About Our Privacy Notice
If you have any questions about our privacy notice, please contact us via our contact form.
© 2020 Tierra Farm.
All Rights Reserved.
